Before using a device, take note of the power socket, reset button, and LED lights.
ご使用になる前に、電源ソケット、リセットボタン、LEDランプの位置を確認してください。
Some devices have the power socket, button and LED lights on an external wire.
一部の機器では、外付けの電源ケーブルに電源プラグ、ボタン、表示ランプが付いています。
Other devices have these areas covered.
他のデバイスでにはこれらの部位をカバーされているかもしれません。
Plug in the supplied power supply to power up the device before using it.
ご使用になる前に、パッケージに付属の電源ケーブルを差し込んで電源を入れてください。
If the device has never been paired, the LEDs will alternately flash and wait to be paired.
カメラがペアリングされていない場合は、表示ランプが交互に点滅し、ペアリング待ちの状態になります。
How to pair the device to my account？
アカウントにデバイスをペアリングするにはどうすればいいですか？
Open the app, log in, click the Add Device button, and select the type of device you want to add.
アプリを開いて、アカウントをログインし、「デバイスを追加」をタップして、追加したいデバイスを選択してください
QR code is the most common and easiest way to set.
QRコードは一般的で簡単に設定できる方法です。
If the LED of the device is not flashing alternately, you can press and hold the reset button to reset it first.
表示ランプは交互に点滅しない場合、リセットボタンを長押して、デバイスをリセットしてください。
Enter your password when setting Wi-Fi  and the username will automatically use the one your phone is currently connected to.
WIFI名は自動入力てきますのでWIFI暗号化キーのみ手で入力する必要があります
If you wish to change your Wi-Fi connection or it is 5G，click the change button.
5Gに接続したい場合またはほかのWIFIに変更したい場合は、変更ボタンをタップしてください。
Next step, a QR code will appear on your App.
そして、QRコードが表示されます。
Place this QR code 3-8 inches in front of the lens of your device and let the camera scan it.
カメラレンズの前にQRコードを約8～20センチに置いて、スキャンしてください。
If the scan is not successful, you can move your phone slightly up and down, back and forth.
QRコードのスキャンにうまく出来ない場合、携帯とカメラの距離を少し調整してください。（近くしたり遠くしたりします）
When the scan is complete, you will hear a prompt and click "Next".
「QRコードのスキャンに成功しました」を聞こえたら、「次へ」をタップしてください。
If having trouble scanning the QR code, double click on the QR code to zoom in and this may make scanning easier.
QRコードのスキャンにうまく出来ない場合、QRコードを2回押せば、大きくなることができます。
Please wait for the device to pair automatically.
自動的にペアリングされるまでお待ちください。
When it is done, you can rename the device to your preference.
WIFI接続に成功したら、カメラ名を自由に設置することができます。
After pairing is complete,  enter the device home list and you can see the added devices,  play live, replay recordings, and adjust settings and other functions.
接続に成功したら、アプリでデバイス画面で追加されたカメラが表示します。リアルタイムの画像、リプレイ、設置などを操作を行うことができます。